fumikomu ze akuseru
press down hard on the gas
kakehiki wa nai sa sou dayo
that's right, there's no compromise
yoru wo nukeru
we'll slip through the night
nejikomu sa saigo ni
at the final moment push hard
sashihiki zero sa sou dayo
that's right, all the way to zero
hibi wo kezuru
until we wipe away the days
kokoro wo sotto
gently open your heart
hiraite gyutto
hiki yosetara
if you pull it close to you
todoku yo kitto
it will reach you, without a doubt
tsutau yo motto sa aa
it will come, closer, now
iki isoide shiboritotte
we're speeding through life, squeezing it for all of its worth
motsureru ashi
our feet are tied
dakedo mae yori zutto sou tooku he
but we still keep going further
ubaitotte tsukandatte
even if I take it back, and grasp it
kimi janai nara
if you're not the one
imi wa nai no sa
there will be no meaning
dakara haruka kanata
and so we'll go far off into the distance
If there's an instance where we
get separated,
don't trust anyone even if they
look like your teammate.
Just like now, there's a possibility
that an enemy will transform
themselves to get close to us!
Yeah.
So what do we do?
We'll decide on a password.
Password?
I'll only say it once so listen closely.
You ask Ninja song, "Ninja Chance".
And the answer is this:
"It is a chance to sneak up where a large
number of enemies are making a scene.
"The quiet place has
no secret hideout.
"It is important for
a Shinobi to know the right time.
"The time when an enemy
is tired and drops his guard.".
That's all.
H-Huge!
T-Tail!
You want our Earth Scroll, don't you?
Well, let's begin...
the battle for the Scrolls.
Life or death!
If this creature doesn't want
to spit me out ...
I'll make it do so at any cost!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
I can't move!
I wanted you to entertain me more.
It's too bad.
Move!
He nullified his fear with pain.
As expected,
he's not your average prey.
Don't come near me!
Don't lower your guard,
not even for a moment...
Prey must always be tense
and flee in desperation
before a predator!
Sorry, Sasuke.
Naruto!
The password... I forgot it!
Naruto Strikes Back!
I'm Not Going
to Run Away!
The password... I forgot it!
That's all right, Naruto!
You're doing great!
Naruto!
I know you're trying to be cool and
rescue us, but...
Don't get involved!
Just run!
She's...
She's on a much different level!
Seems like you brought that
giant snake down brilliantly, Naruto-kun.
No matter how you look,
she looks like a snake...
I get it, it was all the handiwork
of this woman.
Him showing up to help has never
helped any situation...
So what should I do...?
Hey, hey, hey! Evidently you've been
bullying the weakling!
Now that I, Uzumaki Naruto-sama is here,
I'm going to wipe the floor with you!
Damn it! If things continue like this,
all three of us are done for!
What should I do?
Sasuke-kun...
It's no good.
This is the only way.
— Wait.
— Hmm?
— Huh?!
— Huh?
If it's the scroll you want,
I'll give it to you.
I'm asking you.
Just take this and go.
Huh?!
What?!
Hey, Sasuke!
What are you doing?
Why are you giving
our scroll to the enemy?
You, shut up!
What?!
I see...
You're sensible.
The only thing the "prey" can
hope for from the "predator" is
presenting other food in hopes
of being spared, isn't it?
Take it.
Wha...?!
You! Don't interfere!
Don't you understand this situation?!
What're you doing all of a sudden?!
As for me,
I don't remember the password...
So I've got no way to make sure.
But you, you're a fake
Sasuke, aren't you?
Naruto!
W-What are you trying to start?!
You idiot!
I'm the real me!
Liar.
This, this stupid coward is... absolutely...
not the Sasuke I know!
I don't know how strong she is but,
how can you be sure that she'll let us
go if we hand over the Scroll, huh?!
You're the one who's choked and
doesn't understand the situation!
Naruto-kun.
That's correct.
The Scroll.
I could just kill you
and seize it.
Don't mess with me!
Run, Naruto! Stop it!
Damn it!
I've lost confidence in you, Sasuke!
Summoning Jutsu!
Naruto!
There are three corpses.
This is some kind of Ninja Art,
isn't it...?
This is bad.
We have a problem,
right from the start.
I'll be damned.
Inform Anko-san,
the Proctor of the second exam.
Yes, sir!
If you're going to have dumplings,
you've got to have sweet red bean soup.
Okay...
Once I've eaten this,
I should speed through and
go wait at the tower for the kids.
With this program, the quick kids
should clear it soon.
The Leaf Village mark, perfect!
We have a problem, Anko-sama!
Huh? What, so soon?
Corpses! Three of them!
Furthermore, they're strange.
Anyway, please come!
Strange?
I checked their possessions
and identification,
Shinobi from Grass Village
registered in the Chunin Exams, but...
As you can see...
They have no faces.
Yes.
They're smooth and flat,
like they've melted away.
Without a doubt...
This Jutsu is...
that man's...
Why is he here at the exam?
Show me the ID photos of
the three Grass Village Shinobi.
It was on their applications.
Yes!
So this one's face was stolen.
So, back then, they were already...
I'll return... the Kunai knife.
Thank you for your trouble.
We're in big trouble.
Huh?!
You! Let Hokage-sama
know right away!
Make a request to
the ANBU Black Ops
to dispatch two or more squads
to the Forest of Death!
Starting now,
I'm going to follow these guys!
— Got it?
— Yes!
That man...
That man... has come to the Leaf Village!
So cute.
You're such cute prey.
Naruto!
For the time being, eat him.
Shove it!
This brat! He can't be...
Naruto's lost control...
But...
how is he so strong?!
Those eyes...
There's no mistake.
That's... Naruto?!
This just got interesting.
Next up is...
Sasuke-kun.
So what's your move?!
Sasuke-kun!
I have to hurry.
I have a...
bad hunch about this.
Hey. Are you hurt?
Scaredy cat?!
Naruto!
Hey!
Are you hurt...
Scaredy cat?
Sasuke!
This stupid coward is absolutely
not the Sasuke I know!
Huh?!
Damn it!
Let me go!
You stupid snake!
To think that the
nine-tailed brat survived...
When you get excited, a bit
of the nine-tail's power trickles out...
You've grown up in an interesting way.
Look...
The Seal is appearing on
your skin like a tattoo.
Five-Pronged... Sealing!
Sasuke-kun! Help Naruto!
Twelve years since the seal...
Naruto-kun's Chakra and the nine-tail's
Chakra are beginning to act in sync...
But now... you're in the way.
He's gonna fall!
Naruto!
What happened, Sasuke-kun?!
Sasuke-kun...
Naruto's certainly different
from you, Sasuke-kun.
He's a klutz and
kind of gets in the way.
But he's not in the least a coward!
Right?
Isn't that right?
Foolish younger brother.
If you want to kill me,
resent me, hate me and...
continue to live your ugly life.
Flee.
Flee and cling to your life.
No!
As expected of the Uchiha clan...
his blood has begun to stir...
Sasuke-kun!
I should take my time and
confirm his true power.
hey, can you hear it?
nee kikoe masu ka
sora wa hate shinaku aoku sunde ite
the clear, blue sky goes on and on
umi wa kagiri naku koudai de ite
the ocean spans limitlessly
kimi wa itsumade mo egao de ite
please keep that smile on your face forever
janai to nai chau kara
or else I'll cry
mawari o mimawasa naku temo
You won't have to search around you
mou iin da yo
it's all ok now
kono to no naka ni wa minna ga iru kara
everyone is inside this hand
naki taku natte nige taku natte
when you want to cry, and you want to run away
shiawase o wasure te te shimatta ra
when you forget what happiness is
mina utae
just sing
hikari ga umare yami ga umare ta
light is born, and darkness was born
futatsu wa hitotsu
the two are one
HARUMONIA kanji Te TEREPASHII
harmonia, feel the telepathy
nee kikoe masu ka
hey, can you hear it?
I'm an avenger.
In order to defeat my brother,
I have to survive today!
But how can someone who won't risk
his life in a situation like this
be able to defeat my brother?
Calm down, you should be able to see.
There should be some way
to intercept her movements.
Next episode:
"Revive, Sharginan! Finish Move - Fire Element, Dragon Fire Technique!"